Class dismissed.
Let's go.
Want to hit the store?
I'm thirsty.
Sure, I need something too.
Gu Chenyang.
Ms. Du.
I think you're good at chemistry.
How about
being my class rep?
Thanks, Ms. Du.
But I'm already
the physics representative.
You can take on both roles.
I'm also in a club.
I'm afraid I can't handle it.
I'm sorry, sir.
Okay.
Good luck.
That's all
for today's class.
Wanliu
Please tidy up the table.
OK, teacher.
Xu Anbo, wait.
What's up?
I've heard
you played basketball in junior high.
Why don't you join our basketball club?
No, thanks.
I like photography.
I can take photos myself.
Is there a photography club in our school?
No.
That's great.
You should
join our basketball club.
You can take pictures of sports.
It's more exciting, right?
What do you usually take pictures of?
I usually take pictures of...
Brother.
Who is she?
This is my sister, Chi Jia.
Sister?
I take my mom's last name,
and she takes my dad's.
Chi Jia,
this is my deskmate, Lin Qingyuan.
Hello.
I know you.
You're famous for the opening ceremony.
Yeah.
Chi Jia,
what's up?
Dad texted you
to go home early today
and take photos for the new students.
Why didn't you reply?
I know, don't remind me.
Hurry up then.
I'm off, bye.
So this is what you usually shoot.
It's good.
It's a shame
to waste such a good camera.
But it's okay
if you don't have time.
I'll figure it out myself.
I can't force you.
What's wrong?
Lin Qingyuan,
how about
I give it a try?
No need.
You can do it.
Okay.
But let's make a deal.
Call me if you need me.
Don't control me if you don't need me.
No problem. It's a deal.
Let's go.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Come and have a look, please.
One more to go.
Zhou Yang, how about you?
I've contacted all the old members.
They either didn't reply or refused.
Hey, check out the street dance club.
What about Fu Bin Yan?
He's also good at basketball.
Aren't you the "Yi Bei Twins"?
Once Fu Bin Yan decides something,
it's hard to change his mind.
What about Gu Chenyang?
We need to submit the club application tomorrow morning.
Does he have a team spirit?
I'm the one who recruited all these people.
As the temporary leader,
he should do something.
He just came by,
saying he thought of someone who might be interested,
and then hurried off.
Who is it?
Solo time.
Guitar.
Keyboard.
Trumpet.
Very good.
The whole part falls apart.
But it doesn't matter.
It's the first joint practice.
Continue next time.
Yu.
Actually, our band
can't even recruit enough members for the club.
Except for you,
everyone else is just playing around.
How about
we just forget about the band?
Playing in a band,
the most important thing is to have fun.
You guys can join the club if you want.
I'll cover the costs myself.
Don't feel pressured.
You are not welcome here.
You'd better leave.
I'm here to ask you
if you want to play basketball with me.
Are we very familiar?
If it weren't for your basketball team being short of people,
would you have thought of me?
I would rather not join the club
than be your tool to make up the numbers.
Your drumsticks
have been used for a long time, haven't they?
Come to the basketball club,
I'll give you a new one.
Don't be so self-righteous.
This is not the one you gave me.
Well,
either you join my band,
or you
leave here.
Let's have a match.
Match what?
Basketball.
One on one.
If you win, I'll listen to you.
I'll join your band.
If I win,
you'll join the basketball club.
Interesting.
Let's do it.
These two are going one on one.
Let's see who's better.
One on one.
What are you doing?
One-on-one.
You've been a top student
and a tennis player.
Are you still good at basketball?
I'm better than you at playing drums.
Whoever gets 11 points first
wins.
No problem.
You serve first.
As you wish.
Come on!
Gu Chenyang!
Yu, come on!
Excuse me.
Nice shot!
My turn.
So Gu Chenyang was trying to
Li Haoyu.
He can play basketball.
When he was in junior high school,
the basketball club once specially recruited him.
But he thought there were too many rules
and it was not free.
So he didn't go.
Come on!
Good shot!
This is awesome!
Oh my god.
Come on.
Left hand.
Three points.
Nice.
This boy.
What a coincidence.
Bro.
This is the legend
of your school.
It's him.
Amazing!
Why is he here?
So handsome!
Good shot!
Good!
Amazing!
I won!
So handsome!
A bet is a bet.
I'm joining the basketball club.
You three don't have a club.
Do you want to join us?
Yu, we'll listen to you.
Okay.
From now on,
Pulse Star Band
will join the club together.
Welcome to Yibei Basketball Club.
How about two more games?
Let's go.
See you.
You are...
Wait.
How can you...
What do you want to say?
Do you often
play basketball here?
It's really you.
How can it be you?
Don't go, captain.
You admit that I'm the captain now?
Yeah.
You're the captain.
Can you
teach me how to play?
Isn't that what a captain does?
Great, thank you.
Fu Bin Yan.
I didn't expect you to come.
What a game.
Don't you think
Gu Chenyang's style of playing
is very similar to yours?
More like himself.
Every step is planned.
True.
You have more explosive power than him.
How about it?
Do you want to come back?
No.
Zhou Yang
has a new teammate.
You can do better.
Coach.
I'm not sleeping.
Look.
You've really gathered a team.
Coach.
When can we
start training?
You can't.
Here,
read it yourself.
A new notice.
Due to the surge in
club applications this year,
the school board has decided
to conduct a week-long comprehensive evaluation
of all clubs.
Only the top 15
with the highest scores
the top 15 clubs.
What does it mean, Mr. Su?
What's our ranking?
All newly applied clubs
start with zero points.
So,
we're at the bottom.
At the bottom?
We're at the bottom.
It's not too late to run.
I have a buddy in the roller skating club.
He said there are still vacancies.
No.
I've already decided to play basketball.
How could I betray?
You're quite loyal.
It was not easy for us
to re-establish the basketball club.
We have to fight hard
to keep it.
Well said.
How?
We are the last one now.
As you said,
it's now.
There is still a week before the evaluation.
The ranking can change.
Okay.
I've checked the rules.
There are three items in the evaluation.
student votes, teacher votes,
and social contribution.
The first two are short-term breakthroughs.
What does that mean?
It means
one teacher vote
is equivalent to five student votes.
Got it.
Catch the king to catch the thief.
There's only a week.
We must act in groups
to maximize efficiency.
Zhou Yang is the president of the Student Union,
and I'm the representative of the freshman.
We two are a group,
specializing in teacher's votes.
The student's votes are left to you.
The basic goal is 50 votes.
Can you do it?
Of course, a piece of cake.
Did I say I would participate in your canvassing?
If the basketball team is kept,
as long as it doesn't violate the school rules,
I can agree to one of your conditions.
Fifty votes?
That's too little.
Promise me three conditions.
One hundred votes.
One less,
I'll write my name
backwards from now on.
Cool, bro.
Wait a moment.
We need to adjust the grouping.
Li Haoyu, you're with me.
You'll be in charge of the teacher's votes.
Why?
Because the two of you
are uncontrollable.
It's settled.
He got me again.
After the steam is cooled,
liquid water is formed.
That liquid water is distilled water.
Okay.
This is
the whole process of distilling water.
Next class,
you'll go to the lab.
You need to work with your deskmate
to distill water by yourselves.
Okay.
Class is over.
How's the task
on the task I gave you?
Isn't it a bit too abstract?
That's the point.
It's easier to go viral.
Yu,
it's up to you to make it work.
How's it going?
Isn't Li Haoyu and I
doing a great job?
You didn't read
the plan I sent you yesterday?
I did.
I know every word,
but I can't understand
when they are put together.
I can't understand at all.
When people are waiting
or enjoying desserts,
the brain will secrete dopamine.
At this time,
when people are waiting or enjoying desserts.
It's too complicated.
Mine is more direct.
A picture is worth a thousand words.
Now, everyone in our school
knows about our club.
That's true.
But a tactic
is called creative when only one person uses it,
but it's called a cliche when a hundred people use it.
Now all the school clubs
are posting canvassing pictures.
And your work
has become
a small advertisement on the utility pole.
I'm the original creator.
Now the students canvassing
should be down-to-earth.
Their works are just showing off skills,
which have no soul at all.
Unfortunately, the voting machine doesn't recognize the soul.
It only recognizes the result.
Now go to the canteen with me.
What's wrong? Are you hungry?
To carry out my original plan.
Is this thing easy to operate?
I'm afraid I don't understand and will crash into the building.
When you are not skilled at the beginning,
you can find some open space to practice.
Like the basketball court.
The flute is easy to play.
It's just some fingerings.
When you're skilled, you can play some
simple tunes.
I'll teach you.
Take a look at the drone club.
Take a look at the Go club.
You can come to any.
No foundation.
It's completely fine.
Our seniors will provide one-on-one training.
Mr. Gu,
it seems
that everyone is thinking the same as you.
Do we have any alternative plans?
If we wait any longer,
all the good spots will be taken.
We need to make some adjustments.
Wait for me a few minutes.
I can't wait any longer.
This is the last wave of traffic.
the last wave of customers.
Come and take a look.
The best shooter from Yibei Basketball Club
is challenging you.
Our ace player,
Gu Chenyang,
is standing five meters away.
And you,
just need to stand three meters away,
throw the empty bottle into the trash can,
and you'll get your milk tea.
What if I can't make it?
No worries.
As long as you vote
for our basketball club,
you'll still get the milk tea.
It's a win-win.
I see.
Lin Qingyuan,
how is this different from
buying votes with milk tea?
Yeah, it's more fun.
Come on,
it's your turn to show your skills.
Who's first?
Go ahead.
You go first.
Go for it.
So accurate.
Fu Bin Yan,
I think it's fine.
I don't want the milk tea.
Cool.
So accurate.
I'll go first.
Okay, come on.
Ready.
Go.
This works too?
Come on.
Let me hear your cheers.
Gu Chenyang.
Ready.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Let's go!
The "submarine" is here!
Go where?
We're just getting started!
Wait a minute!
Who did you say was here?
The "submarine"!
What's going on
with all these people?
What's going on?
Why are you all blocking here?
Mr. Qian.
You two explain it.
We are playing games in the basketball club.
Playing games?
Using milk tea
to exchange votes.
Mr. Qian.
Our intention was to promote the club.
but the method...
Gu Chenyang,
it's just the beginning of the term.
How could you be misled?
Sir, I...
Sir, this has nothing to do with him.
Shut up!
Give it to me.
Students,
I hereby announce that
the basketball club
cheated to get votes,
violating fairness.
All votes are invalid.
Sir, we...
I hope you can learn a lesson.
Dismissed.
Go away.
Go.
Stop.
Come here.
You two.
clean up this mess
before the next class.
Make sure it's spotless.
What are you waiting for?
Li Haoyu,
show yourself.
Come to my office after school.
We'll settle
your debts.
You guys didn't even run.
You didn't make it clear.
What didn't I make clear?
Wait a moment, you three.
Who will pay the bill?
This one.
Oh, no.
It's all over.
The money spent on milk tea was wasted.
The tickets are gone too.
It was my money.
Why do you care?
I'll transfer the money to you later.
It's not a big deal.
By the way,
how are you doing
with the voting?
Why did the director come
so fast?
Yeah.
He asked you
to go to the office.
Did you get into trouble again?
Not
really.
Ms. Wang.
This year's club applications
are up by a dozen.
Just the initial screening
is giving me a headache.
How's the basketball club coming along?
Still working on it.
Ms. Wang,
as an important sports team,
is an essential sports team
for every middle school.
It's indispensable.
Zhou Yang,
I know what you're thinking,
but I oversee all the clubs.
It's not appropriate for me
to vote for you.
Alright,
could you deliver these
to the principal's office?
Thank you.
My pleasure, Ms. Wang.
Haoyu, I...
Come in.
Good afternoon, sir.
Enriching your soul?
What can I do for you?
You're here to deliver an edict?
No, no,
I'm here to report my ideological achievements.
Yibei's key inspection and discipline maintenance
and discipline in Yibei.
That's right.
Look.
The crooked tree at the east wall
is a holy land for truants.
Although the back window of the western warehouse
is sealed,
there is still a loophole.
The back alley of the canteen
is the best place to trade snacks.
With it,
you can catch
students breaking rules.
Li Haoyu, what are you doing?
I used to be immature
and always made you angry.
Now I understand,
what the school needs is order,
and I'm willing to be your enforcer.